NOTHING! I CAN'T FIND ANYTHING
THAT I WANT TO EAT.
EVERYTHING MAKES ME NAUSEOUS.
BEING PREGNANT
IS NO PIECE OF CAKE.
OOH, CAKE.
NO.
SEE?
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
GOD... OOH!
WHAT IS THAT SMELL?
IT'S COMING FROM
THE BATHROOM. OOH!
WOW, PREGNANCY DOES GIVE YOU
SOME WEIRD CRAVINGS.
( knocking )
Joey:
YEAH?
IT'S ME, PHOEBE.
THERE'S SOMETHING
IN HERE I WANT TO EAT.
WHAT, WHAT...?
WHAT SMELLS SO GOOD?
IS IT THE SHAMPOO?
IT'S GUAVA.
NO!
EWW!
OH, WAIT, WAIT!
IS IT MY
BOLOGNA
SANDWICH?
YES. YES, YES, YES!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT THE BABY WANTS BOLOGNA.
THE BABY WANTS ME
TO EAT MEAT!
I CAN'T EAT MEAT!
OH, WAIT, WAIT!
MAYBE IT'S THE PICKLE.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
WHAT ARE YOU WRITING?
WELL, JOSHUA'S
COMING IN TOMORROW
AND SINCE I DON'T
HAVE THE GUTS
TO ASK HIM OUT
I'M GOING
TO SELL HIM A COAT
AND PUT THIS NOTE
IN THE POCKET.
OH, YEAH?
"JOSHUA,
GIVE ME A CALL SOMETIME.
"GUYS LIKE YOU...
NEVER GO OUT OF STYLE."
WHAT DID YOU THROW AWAY?
Chandler:
HI, GUYS.
HI.
HEY, WHAT HAVE YOU GUYS
BEEN UP TO?
OH, WE WENT TO SEE
A COLLECTION OF
VICTORIAN DOORKNOBS
AT THE COOPER
HEWITT MUSEUM.
WITHOUT ME?!
YEAH. MY UNCLE
DRAGGED US THERE
BUT IT ACTUALLY TURNED OUT
TO BE REALLY INTERESTING.
THEY WERE SO ORNATE
AND BEAUTIFUL.
I MEAN, LOOK AT THAT.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW MUSEUMS WORK IN ENGLAND
BUT HERE, YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO TAKE STUFF.
I, UH, I GOT IT
FROM THE GIFT SHOP.
THEY HAVE REALLY
LAX SECURITY THERE.
IT'S A JOKE.
ALL RIGHT.
RIGHT. I'VE GOT TO BE OFF.
WELL, SEE YOU.
BYE-BYE, THEN.
All:
BYE.
WELL... HEY, YOU GUYS
SEEM TO BE HAVING A GOOD TIME.
OH, YEAH.
SHE'S-SHE'S AMAZING
AND-AND SHE'S SO MUCH FUN,
YOU KNOW?
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHEN I'M WITH HER, I'M FUN.
( laughs weakly )
I EVEN SIGNED UP
FOR HELICOPTER CLASSES.
SHE'S LEAVING IN TWO DAYS.
I DON'T HAVE
TO DO IT.
WOW. TWO DAYS.
YOU MUST BE BUMMED.
SHE'S GOT TO GO BACK TO LONDON
BUT I'VE BEEN PREPARED FOR THIS
FROM THE START.
WE BOTH KNEW
WE HAD TWO WEEKS TOGETHER
AND THEN THAT'S IT, YOU KNOW?
HEY, THAT'S WHAT
ALL MY RELATIONSHIPS ARE LIKE.
YES, BUT IN ROSS' CASE
THEY BOTH KNOW
IN TWO WEEKS THAT'S IT.
PHEEBS!
HEY!
OH, HELLO! HELLO!
I KNOW, I
KNOW. YEAH.
SO, THE BABY
IS TOTALLY
CRAVING MEAT.
THIS AFTERNOON,
I TRIED TRICKING IT.
I MADE IT A SOY BURGER
SO MAYBE IT WOULD THINK
IT WAS GETTING MEAT
AND I GOT NAUSEOUS.
WELL, MAYBE THAT'S BECAUSE
SOY BURGERS SUCK.
BEING PREGNANT
IS HARD ON YOUR TUMMY.
BUT AT LEAST YOU GET
THAT COOL, "PREGNANT LADY GLOW."
OH, THAT'S SWEAT.
YOU THROW UP ALL MORNING.
YOU'LL HAVE
THAT GLOW, TOO.
OKAY.
OH, UH, HERE'S
THAT TRENCH COAT
THAT YOU WANTED.
OH, GREAT, GREAT.
WOW. YEAH.
IT'S COMFORTABLE.
YEAH.
MAN...
I COULD REALLY FLASH SOMEBODY
IN THIS THING.
OH, NO, NO. THEY
DON'T WANT YOU
TO PUT YOUR HANDS
IN THE POCKETS
UNTIL YOU ARE OUT OF THE STORE.
WHY NOT?
WELL, BECAUSE...
WE GET A LOT OF...
YOU KNOW,
THEY RUIN IT FOR EVERYBODY.
I KNOW.
I WORE THAT CASHMERE SWEATER
ON A DATE LAST NIGHT.
OH.
YEAH.
IT WAS THE FIRST DATE
SINCE THE DIVORCE.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS.
SO, DO YOU LOVE HER?
NO, NO, NO.
SHE'S NICE,
BUT IT JUST MADE ME REALIZE
I'M JUST NOT READY TO...
TO BE DATING, YOU KNOW?
HUH.
WELL...
UH...
THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S INTERESTING.
HEY, WHOA. HEY...
WHAT WAS THAT?
OH, IT'S JUST AN
ANTI-THEFT DEVICE.
THEN, UH, WH-WHAT'S THIS?
WELL, YOU NEED THAT,
YOU NEED THAT, TOO
'CAUSE, OBVIOUSLY,
A THIEF COULD JUST
TEAR THIS RIGHT UP.
WE HAVE TO HAVE
A PARTY TONIGHT.
ACTUALLY, WE HAVE TO HAVE ONE
IN FIVE MINUTES
SO, EVERYBODY
CANCEL YOUR PLANS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WE HAVE TO HAVE A SURPRISE
BON VOYAGE PARTY FOR EMILY
BUT IT'S ACTUALLY FOR JOSHUA.
LOOK. HE SAID
HE'S NOT READY TO DATE
SO I HAD TO INVITE HIM
TO A PARTY
IF I WANTED TO SEE HIM
OUTSIDE OF WORK
AND NOW I HAVE CREATED
THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
TO SEDUCE HIM.
WELL, AS MUCH
AS I'D LIKE TO MEET JOSH
AND WARN HIM...
EMILY AND I
AREN'T GOING TO BE HERE.
I MEAN, SHE'S GOING
TO COME BY FIRST TO SAY GOOD-BYE
AND THEN I'VE GOT
A WHOLE SPECIAL EVENING PLANNED
SO, SORRY, NO PARTY.
AW!
HELLO.
SURPRISE!
NO ONE'S EVER THROWN ME
A SURPRISE PARTY BEFORE!
WELL, IT WAS ALL ROSS' IDEA.
YOU'RE SO SWEET...
AND I'M SO SURPRISED.
YOU REALLY DIDN'T KNOW?
WHY ARE YOU OVER HERE
IF JOSHUA'S ALL
THE WAY OVER THERE?
UH, BECAUSE I'M TRYING
TO PLAY HARD-TO-GET.
HE'S LOOKING.
SAY SOMETHING FUNNY.
LIKE WHAT?
( theatrical laugh )
WH-WH-WHAT'S
SO FUNNY?
I SAID "LIKE WHAT?"
WELL, THAT'S A THINKER.
OKAY. THIS PLAYING
HARD-TO-GET THING
IS NOT WORKING.
HAND ME THOSE CHERRIES.
OKAY.
HI.
HEY.
CARE FOR A CHERRY?
OH, NO, THANKS.
YOU KNOW, I CAN TIE
ONE OF THESE INTO A KNOT
USING JUST MY TONGUE.
( choking )
( coughing )
YOU OKAY?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
SO, WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET GOING SOON.
OH, BUT THE PARTY'S
ONLY JUST GETTING STARTED.
WE HAVE TO BE
AT THE FOUR SEASONS FOR DRINKS
IN-- OH!-- 15 MINUTES,
AND THEN, UH, YOU KNOW
THEN THE PLAZA FOR DINNER.
SO, WHY DID YOU PLAN A PARTY
AT THE SAME TIME?
NO, NO, NO. NO.
UM, ACTUALLY,
AMERICAN SURPRISE PARTIES
ARE-ARE-ARE VERY SHORT.
IT'S USUALLY "SURPRISE!"
AND THEN, "OH, MY GOD,
I'M SO SURPRISED. GOOD-BYE."
ROSS, I'M HAVING
SUCH A GREAT TIME.
YOUR SISTER
HAS JUST BEEN
TELLING ME
THAT YOU USED TO DRESS
UP LIKE LITTLE OLD LADIES
AND HOST MAKE-BELIEVE
TEA PARTIES.
MONICA SAID THAT,
DID SHE?
YEAH.
OH, YEAH.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO PUT ON TOP OF THAT?
A LITTLE SALAMI.
OOH, YEAH, YEAH.
THEN, UM, WHAT GOES
ON TOP OF THE SALAMI?
OH, PASTRAMI.
OOH, YEAH.
YOU'RE A GENIUS.
OH, COULD SOMEBODY
GIVE ME A HAND WITH THE ZIPPER?
UP!
YOU CHANGED?
YEAH. I DECIDED
I NEEDED MY LUCKY DRESS.
AND "LUCKY" MEANS
MORE CLEAVAGE?
IT DOES FOR ME.
OH, GOD, LOOK AT HIM!
HE'S SO CUTE!
I JUST WANT TO GO
OVER THERE AND GRAB
HIM AND KISS HIM!
HOW COULD I KISS HIM
WITHOUT LETTING HIM
KNOW THAT I LIKE HIM?!
HEY, I KNOW
HOW YOU CAN GET HIM.
TAKE OFF YOUR BRA.
WHAT?
THIS SCENE
IN FOOTLOOSE...
FLASHDANCE.
YEAH. WITH THAT
PLUMBER GIRL...
SHE WAS A WELDER.
WERE YOU, LIKE,
IN THE MOVIE, OR...?
ANYWAY, SHE TAKES OFF HER BRA
UNDER THE SHIRT
AND PULLS IT OUT THE SLEEVE.
VERY SEXY, AND CLASSY.
OR, IF YOU WANT
TO KISS HIM
UM, YOU COULD
USE MISTLETOE.
IT'S NOT CHRISTMAS.
SPIN THE BOTTLE.
HE'S NOT 11.
THANK YOU SO
MUCH FOR THIS.
IT WAS REALLY SO
THOUGHTFUL OF YOU.
WHAT, YOU'RE LEAVING?!
WE HAVE
SOMETHING
TO GET TO.
YEAH. I THINK I'M
GOING TO TAKE OFF,
TOO, ACTUALLY.
OH, YOU GUYS,
YOU CAN'T LEAVE YET!
YOU HAVE TO STAY!
WE... WE'VE GOT
THE WHOLE BIG THING PLANNED.
WHAT BIG THING?
SO, SPIN THE BOTTLE
WORKS LIKE THIS:
I SPIN THE BOTTLE...
LANDS ON GUNTHER,
SO I WOULD HAVE TO KISS GUNTHER.
ALL RIGHT.
WHO WANTS TO GO FIRST?
I'LL GO.
OKAY!
EMILY! WHOO!
WELCOME TO AMERICA.
ALL RIGHT.
( Monica squealing )
TWO IN A ROW.
YOU GOT TO USE
YOUR TONGUES NOW.
ALL RIGHT.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS?
OKAY. TH-THAT'S
ENOUGH, YOU KNOW?
LET'S LET
SOMEONE
ELSE PLAY.
IF YOU DIDN'T WANT TO PLAY
THEN WHY'D YOU COME
TO THE PARTY?
OKAY. MY TURN!
OH!
LOOK AT THAT!
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD, THE
BABY JUST KICKED!
OH!
IT'S OKAY, IT'S OKAY!
IF IT KICKED ONCE,
IT'LL KICK AGAIN!
( all clamoring )
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, EVERYBODY JUST REMEMBER
WHERE THEY WERE SITTING.
IT WAS A BUG.
YOU KNOW WHY I'M NEVER
GOING TO EAT MEAT?
'CAUSE IT'S MURDER.
IT'S COLD-BLOODED MURDER.
OKAY.
THERE'S A PHOEBE
ON MY SANDWICH.
MMM.
PHOEBE, WH-WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
I CAN'T HELP IT.
I NEED THE MEAT.
THE BABY NEEDS THE MEAT.
YOU KNOW HOW
WHEN YOU'RE DATING SOMEONE
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO CHEAT ON THEM
UNLESS IT'S
WITH SOMEONE REALLY HOT?
YEAH. TOTALLY.
ALL RIGHT. OKAY.
WELL, THIS IS
THE SAME KIND OF DEAL.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO DO
SOMETHING WRONG...
DO IT RIGHT.
SO YOU FEEL BETTER NOW?
YEAH, BUT AT WHAT COST?
SIX MORE MONTHS,
THREE MEALS A DAY.
I'M GOING TO EAT LIKE,
YOU KNOW...
MILLIONS OF COWS.
HEY, WHAT IF I SAID I COULD
EVEN THINGS OUT FOR YOU...
MEAT-WISE?
WHAT?
I EAT A LOT OF MEAT, RIGHT?
BUT SUPPOSE, UNTIL
THE BABY'S BORN
I LAID OFF IT.
NO EXTRA ANIMALS WOULD DIE.
YOU'D JUST BE
EATING MY ANIMALS.
JOEY, I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I COULD BE A VEGETARIAN.
THERE'S NO MEAT IN BEER, RIGHT?
WE CAN STILL MAKE DINNER
IF WE SKIP APPETIZERS
AND ASK FOR OUR CHECK
RIGHT AWAY.
WELL, WE CAN'T
GO NOW.
LOOKS LIKE
RACHEL'S GOING
TO PUT ON A SKIT.
OH, MY GOD.
HAVE YOU LOST YOUR MIND?
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I AM FINALLY
THINKING CLEARLY.
MY LUCKY DRESS WASN'T
WORKING OUT TOO WELL FOR ME
BUT FOR FOUR YEARS,
THIS BABY NEVER MISSED.
RACHEL, RACHEL, RACHEL,
I CANNOT... I CAN'T LET...
ACTUALLY, I KIND OF WANT
TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
HEY.
HI.
NICE, UH... COSTUME.
OH, YEAH.
WELL, I WANTED TO GIVE EMILY
A BIG, AMERICAN
GOOD-BYE CHEER.
SO, OKAY.
WHOO!
READY?
OKAY.
GIVE ME AN "E."
All:
"E"
GIVE ME AN "M."
"M"
GIVE ME AN "I."
"I"
GIVE ME AN "L."
"L"
GIVE ME A "Y."
"Y"
WHAT DO YOU GET?
EMILY.
WHOO!
EMILY!
( yells )
OKAY, SO THAT'S ME
AS A CHEERLEADER.
TA-DUM!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
FINE. I'M FINE.
I JUST LOOSENED A TOOTH.
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I HAVE A DENTIST.
I'LL GO PUT SOME ICE ON IT.
EXCUSE ME.
OKAY. WHAT DO I DO NOW?
I THINK YOU'RE DONE.
OKAY. TIME
TO TAKE OFF THE BRA.
UH, THAT WAS...
REALLY, UH, GREAT
BUT I-I GOT TO
TAKE OFF, ACTUALLY.
( whispers ):
TAKE THE BRA OFF.
ALL RIGHT. COME ON.
LET'S GO GET YOUR COAT.
OKAY.
RACHEL IS MY GIRLFRIEND.
SO THIS WAS,
UH, REALLY FUN.
OH, YEAH. IT'S REAL FUN.
YOU KNOW, THIS BRA...
IS REALLY BOTHERING ME.
YOU KNOW, THIS USED TO BE
MY BEDROOM.
YEAH.
LOT OF MEMORIES IN HERE.
LOT OF MEMORIES.
IF THESE WALLS COULD TALK,
YOU KNOW WHAT THEY'D SAY?
WANT TO HEAR SOME MEMORIES?
NEED A...
NEED A LITTLE HAND THERE?
OH, NO, NO.
I GOT THIS ALL UNDER CONTROL.
YOU REALLY DON'T
SEEM LIKE YOU DO.
THAT'S...
( grunts )
( yells )
FORGET IT!
( groans loudly )
THIS IS... FOR...
THIS IS NOT HOW THIS
WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
WHAT WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN?
CAN YOU NOT LOOK AT ME
WHEN I SAY THIS?
I THOUGHT THAT IF
I COULD GET YOU HERE
I COULD SEDUCE YOU.
HUH.
( groaning sigh )
UH... I-I DON'T WEAR...
SUITS TO WORK
AND I BOUGHT SIX OF THEM
FROM YOU.
WELL, I'M SORRY.
I THOUGHT YOU NEEDED THEM.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
MY POINT IS
I KEPT COMING BACK
BECAUSE...
I WANTED TO SEE YOU.
WHY?
BECAUSE I-I LIKE YOU.
YOU LIKE ME?
YEAH.
I MEAN, YOU'RE-YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL
AND SMART AND SOPHISTICATED.
LOT OF THIS ISN'T, YOU KNOW,
BASED ON TONIGHT.
BUT-BUT YOU LIKE ME?
OH, MY GOD,
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
ALL THIS TIME
I LIKED YOU AND YOU LIKED ME.
BUT...
NO, NO. DON'T SAY "BUT."
NO, NO. BUT'S NEVER GOOD.
JUST LET'S LEAVE IT AT
I LIKE YOU AND YOU LIKE ME.
OKAY. UH, HOWEVER...
NOW, SEE, THAT'S A FANCY "BUT."
MY MARRIAGE, LIKE,
JUST ENDED
AND I'M REALLY NOT READY
TO GET INTO ANYTHING YET.
BUT...
I'M SORRY.
I... I JUST NEED
A LITTLE TIME.
OKAY.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
I WAS LOOKING
FOR YOU BEFORE.
JOSHUA'S GONE
SO YOU AND EMILY ARE FREE TO GO.
IT'S OKAY.
SHE'S STILL IN THERE
ENJOYING HER FAKE PARTY
AND, UH, IT'S TOO LATE
TO DO ANY OF THE STUFF
I HAD PLANNED, SO...
OH, ROSS, I'M SORRY.
I COMPLETELY RUINED
YOUR EVENING.
( clears throat )
YEAH.
WELL, IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER,
I MADE A FOOL OF MYSELF.
HELPS A LITTLE.
IS THERE ROOM ON THAT STEP
FOR A PATHETIC LOSER?
YEAH. HAVE A SEAT.
OH...
I'M SO SORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, IT WAS JUST
A TWO-WEEK THING ANYWAY.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT IT TO END
THIS WAY, YOU KNOW?
OR MAYBE YOU DIDN'T
WANT IT TO END.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU SEEM TO REALLY LIKE HER.
YEAH. I REALLY DO.
YEAH, BUT WHAT AM I
GOING TO DO?
I MEAN, WE BOTH AGREED
IT WAS GOING TO BE
A TWO-WEEK THING.
YOU KNOW, NO COMMITMENT.
ROSS, THAT GIRL JUST SPENT
THE ENTIRE EVENING
TALKING TO YOUR FRIENDS
ASKING TO HEAR
STORIES ABOUT YOU
LOOKING THROUGH
MONICA'S PHOTO ALBUMS.
I MEAN, YOU DON'T DO THAT
IF YOU'RE JUST IN IT
FOR TWO WEEKS.
YOU THINK?
LOOK, YOU'VE GOT,
LIKE, 14 HOURS
UNTIL SHE HAS TO
BE AT THE AIRPORT
AND YOU'RE SITTING HERE
IN A HALLWAY WITH A...
28-YEAR-OLD CHEERLEADER
WITH A FAT LIP.
( chuckles )
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
YEAH.
THANKS.
WHAT PHOTO ALBUM WAS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WAS YOU
AND A BUNCH OF ALBINO KIDS.
OH, MY GOD.
THOSE WEREN'T ALBINO KIDS.
THAT WAS COMPUTER CAMP.
RACH.
HEY.
YOU'RE A PATHETIC LOSER, RIGHT?
( laughing ):
OH, YEAH.
SIT.
HI.
OH, MY GOD.
JOSHUA.
LOOK...
ALL THOSE THINGS I SAID
ABOUT NOT BEING READY...
THEY'RE NOT TRUE.
NO. THEY'RE-THEY'RE
ALL TRUE.
OH.
BUT...
OH, I LOVE THAT "BUT."
UM, DO YOU WANT
TO GO INSIDE AND
GET SOME COFFEE?
YEAH.
OKAY.
EVERY TIME.
WHAT DO YOU GOT?
PASTRAMI.
YEAH.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT
GOES GOOD WITH THAT?
MM-HMM. CORNED BEEF.
OOH, I WAS GOING
TO SAY BOLOGNA
BUT THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
HEY, HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
OF THAT SMOKED TURKEY?
OKAY.
( laughing )
OH, MAMA.
HOW... WHEN-WHEN
IS THE BABY DUE?
SIX MONTHS.
OH... HEY, NOW
IF A COW SHOULD DIE
OF NATURAL CAUSES
I CAN HAVE ONE
OF THOSE, RIGHT?
NOT IF I GET THERE FIRST.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]